export const Questions = [
    {
        img:"https://media.gettyimages.com/photos/scientist-hand-holding-test-tube-with-blood-in-laboratory-picture-id1182362201?k=20&m=1182362201&s=612x612&w=0&h=rnEf1s4yoF5jq3whj1YXFBPM3vGq1mc0-XP-A-c7FaU=",
        prompt : "1 . Which is not considered a common method of transmission for HIV?",
        optionA:"blood",
        optionB:"genital secretions",
        optionC:"breast milk",
        optionD:"urine",
        answer:"D"
    },
    {
        img:"https://media.gettyimages.com/illustrations/infection-artwork-illustration-id160935987?k=20&m=160935987&s=612x612&w=0&h=RU5OVoHc4KdUcbTc3lLAbNBnknX2b0crExuTJ23fJug=",
        prompt : "2 . About one-fourth of all people with HIV/AIDS areâ€¦",
        optionA:"homosexual men",
        optionB:"living in southern U.S. states",
        optionC:"over the age of 50",
        optionD:"bisexual women",
        answer:"C"
    },
    {
        img:"https://media.gettyimages.com/photos/spreading-picture-id172153877?k=20&m=172153877&s=612x612&w=0&h=JTXv3w53cL_U5xxHfX22_91UZisDFLgLciybtY_cqCQ=",
        prompt : "3 . What does it mean to be HIV-positive?",
        optionA:"It means that you have AIDS.",
        optionB:"It means that two tests have been identified positive for HIV.",
        optionC:"the means the virus cannot be passed to another person",
        optionD:"none of the above",
        answer:"B"
    },
    {
        img:"https://media.gettyimages.com/photos/microscopic-view-of-3d-spherical-viruses-picture-id1213929556?k=20&m=1213929556&s=612x612&w=0&h=oHBhK40-D3kmU7BBADXKzULh75d-znkO88_Gl0oLEMk=",
        prompt : "4 . Where did HIV originate?",
        optionA:"A chimpanzee",
        optionB:"Mad cow disease",
        optionC:"A strain of the hepatitis virus",
        optionD:"All of the above",
        answer:"A"
    },
    {
        img:"https://media.gettyimages.com/photos/young-woman-with-red-aids-awareness-ribbon-picture-id1092274026?k=20&m=1092274026&s=612x612&w=0&h=l2pyf0Yql7ZzUpOHEci10vj3LKZECtk4kfxYxq8tH6Y=",
        prompt : "5 . What is AIDS?",
        optionA:"A fungal infection",
        optionB:"A rare blood cancer caused by HIV",
        optionC:"A group of diseases caused by HIV",
        optionD:"The final stage of HIV",
        answer:"D"
    },
    {
        img:"https://media.gettyimages.com/photos/migrant-worker-wears-a-red-ribbon-during-an-event-organized-by-the-picture-id56313604?k=20&m=56313604&s=612x612&w=0&h=2OLQFiD8cw2aJI3qQznGAUdtAhmN8hZSdE_xdfD7sEY=",
        prompt : "6 . what are T cells ?",
        optionA:"T cells are a type of white blood cell",
        optionB:"T cells scan cells for abnormalities",
        optionC:"T cells coordinate immune responses",
        optionD:"All of the above",
        answer:"D"
    },
    {
        img:"https://media.gettyimages.com/illustrations/hivirus-3d-rendering-illustration-id686736669?k=20&m=686736669&s=612x612&w=0&h=MmfSxL5jZWaNZ3t4oqm_XJATT8tVg0LUa6ZTHJ0bxhI=",
        prompt : "7 . how does HIV becomes AIDS ?",
        optionA:"HIV attacks the T cells",
        optionB:"HIV makes multiple copies of itself",
        optionC:"HIV destroys cells in the body",
        optionD:"All of the above",
        answer:"D"
    },
    {
        img:"https://media.gettyimages.com/photos/cropped-hands-holding-aids-awareness-ribbon-picture-id1029501082?k=20&m=1029501082&s=612x612&w=0&h=UeK3SXOPp219Fw5vzQEBIDrREZ5n1ZHlzaMA88HFJeM=",
        prompt : "8 . How many stages are there in HIV infection",
        optionA:"One",
        optionB:"Two",
        optionC:"Three",
        optionD:"Four",
        answer:"C"
    },
    {
        img:"https://media.gettyimages.com/illustrations/infection-artwork-illustration-id513089725?k=20&m=513089725&s=612x612&w=0&h=Ic2tRwcotK9qCtoNh_nVJg_n-rp1m14ElcrF2fphWN0=",
        prompt : "9 . When did the world health organization first proposed a definition for AIDS ?",
        optionA:"1950",
        optionB:"1986",
        optionC:"1965",
        optionD:"1976",
        answer:"B"
    },
    {
        img:"https://media.gettyimages.com/illustrations/virus-similar-to-hi-virus-3d-rendering-illustration-id673116141?k=20&m=673116141&s=612x612&w=0&h=oX2LF6lxUeP5uRjwJj2fgOUmhx1FjonPTFtN-LDwriE=",
        prompt : "10 . Which is the second most common way of spreading HIV ?",
        optionA:"Sexual intercourse with HIV infected",
        optionB:"Sharing needles",
        optionC:"Sharing food",
        optionD:"From infected mother to child",
        answer:"B"
    }
]